We just can't anymore.
Well, good luck with your next party.
Though I don't know who'd recruit a loser
who can't level up anymore
because of their bad build.
They say relationships only last
as long as the money does.
The skill point system is brutal.
I wasn't expecting
a Blood-Soaked Sword to drop.
It's because of my skills, you know.
They worked, didn't they?
Because of you, huh?
We finally got this rare drop after
visiting the Dungeon a bunch of times.
I'm not sure that it really was
because of your skills.
Could it be?
Does she have that skill tree?
Who'd kick someone with that skill tree?
But based on that conversation,
that must be it.
If I'm right, she's got
a broken skill tree.
I'm sorry for being selfish!
You never have to pay me again!
Please keep me in the party!
Wh-Who are you?!
Please!
Please! Will you form a party with me?
A p-p-party?!
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 6\h\h\hRuche the Pierrot
How did this happen?
Some days are just like that.
Please! You won't regret it!
Let's form a party!
How about an 80/20 split?
I couldn't do 20% forever.
I couldn't afford to support myself.
You'd get 80%, of course.
I'm fine with 20%.
I-Is that okay?
That's what you meant?!
P-Please calm down.
First, could you let go of my hand?
Oh, sorry.
Hey, what the hell is this?
Who the hell do you think you are?
I'm Elymas.
I overheard that she's leaving your party.
So I came to scout her.
Are you out of your mind?
She's so piss-poor in combat
that she can't level properly.
That's fine. It's not a problem.
I hope you don't regret it.
You'll be saving us some guilt
if you take in that useless girl.
Go ahead.
Take her.
I'm not asking for your permission.
What?
Panic
What level are you?
Do you have other party members?
I'm a level 23 solo Heavy Knight.
I'm an E-rank adventurer.
A level 23 solo Heavy Knight?
Someone your level
should know how useless she is.
E-Excuse me...
I'm actually only level 13.
Maybe this isn't a good idea.
It's fine. It's not a problem.
Hey, Cline.
What, Reiss?
Isn't it strange for an E-rank adventurer
to try so desperately to recruit Ruche?
Whisper
Maybe her skills are
more useful than we realize.
Whisper
Did I come across as too desperate?
They didn't do jack shit.
Whisper
They're pointless.
But...
What are you saying, Reiss?
Just keep your mouth shut and let her go.
It's better for us if she leaves quietly.
Just think about it.
A Heavy Knight couldn't have
reached level 23 on his own.
He's either bullshitting
or was kicked from his party.
Whisper
Or he's hitting on her.
If nothing else, Ruche has a pretty face.
Whisper
I suppose.
Besides, this works out great.
Whisper
We wouldn't want the rumor to spread that
we kicked someone for their bad build.
That's true.
Whisper
Elymas, we were waiting
for someone like you.
Take good care of Ruche.
I-In that case...
I gratefully accept your kind offer.
I look forward
to working with you, Mr. Elymas.
Yeah.
Likewise, Ruche.
I just gained my first party member.
Congrats on your new party.
You've never bought a decent
weapon, right, Ruche?
This 100,000 gold is
a parting gift from us.
Use it well.
Th-Thank you, Mr. Cline...
Don't pick that up.
What?
Cline, was it?
Pick up the coins you threw on the ground.
Even a child can do that.
You call this a gift when you threw it
on the ground? Yeah, right.
Let's go, Ruche.
B-But 100,000 gold is a lot of money...
It's best not to owe
anything to guys like him.
Huh?
O-Okay.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Have fun being useless together
with your defective classes!
Let's go, Reiss.
Can I have this money?
O-Of course not! It's mine!
Ugh, you're so stingy.
Sure, no problem.
Thanks for waiting.
Hey.
Let's do a more lucrative quest next time.
Be right there. Please be patient.
Thank you for inviting me
to join your party, Mr. Elymas!
But I still don't think I'm strong enough.
Don't worry.
If we kill monsters suited to your
skill trees, you'll level up in—
So, actually...
That got me thinking, Mr. Elymas...
Did you help me because
you fell in love at first sight?
What do you mean?
I've been wondering why someone
above my level would stand up for me,
and that's all I could come up with.
I mean, I am cute.
Um, and I think you're very handsome.
But maybe we could start out as friends.
I'm not that easy.
Tee-hee
Ruche.
You have the Lady Luck
skill tree, don't you?
Skill Tree: [Lady Luck]
Huh?
What?
Am I being hasty?
We were destined to meet.
I wouldn't say that.
Again!
Ruche.
You have the Lady Luck
skill tree, don't you?
Skill Tree: [Lady Luck]
Huh?
What?
In Magic World,
Dungeons (Dreamholes)
Dungeons are the nightmares
are the nightmares of the
sleeping God of Creation, Alxeros.
of the sleeping God of Creation, Alxeros.
Alxeros created countless gods and
worlds from nothing over an eternity.
But Alxeros, who'd remained the absolute
god on high throughout that time,
lost his mind and was sealed away
by the very gods he created.
However, Alxeros's nightmares
are beginning to affect reality.
His nightmares are creating gates
in the real world
that produce aberrant monsters and demons.
There it is.
Huh?
Those are Dungeons or Dreamholes.
Angel's Playbox Entrance
Angel's Playbox Entrance.
Recommended level: 50.
Recommended Level: 50
Are you sure you want me, Mr. Elymas?
I mean, just look at me.
Ruche Luvis
Attack
Defense
Magic
Speed
Attack
Defense
Magic
Speed
Equipment
Ironpiercer
Special Skills
Cat's Paw
Titles
Rank F Adventurer
Common Skills
Dice Thrust
See?
You really shouldn't be
showing people that.
Seriously?!
It's fine. I know you won't tell anyone.
Besides, I'd rather you abandon me now
than get your hopes up
just to disappoint you later.
I can't even use my only attack skill,
Dice Thrust, unless I roll a six.
Miss.
Dice Thrust [Common Skill]
A thrusting skill
Rolls a six-sided die and grants an
additional effect based on the rolled result
If only I'd taken The Fool's Acrobatics
or put points into Attack Booster.
Skill Tree: Pierrot
Remaining Skill Points:
The Fool's Acrobatics
Lady Luck
Attack Booster
I really screwed up, huh?
It's fine.
Ruche, I need you.
What? Wh-What do you mean by that?
Um, I'm not too familiar
with that sort of thing.
I need you to be more direct
or I won't understand.
Oh, um... but I shouldn't say that.
It's not fair, is it?
What? Oh, right.
We're going to grind out an easy
30 million gold and get you to level 30.
What?!
How the heck are we gonna do that?!
Let's go.
Okay.
The recommended level is 50,
but I'm familiar with
the monsters that spawn here.
We won't encounter any serious danger.
We're just going to grind levels
on the upper floors.
I'll draw enemies to me, so use that
Ironpiercer knife to defeat them.
Ironpiercer
I made the decision to come this far.
You even bought me this expensive knife.
I can't wimp out now!
Ironpiercer.
Ironpiercer Recommended Level: 18
Attack: +3
Market Price: 550,000G
This knife is effective against tough opponents
When damage is applied, reduce the target's
defense by 15% before calculating damage
Attack +3. Market price: 550,000 gold.
This knife is effective
against tough opponents.
When damage is applied,
reduce the target's Defense by
15% before damage calculation.
You can count on me, Mr. Elymas!
I'll do what I can to live up to your
inexplicable confidence and expectations!
Uh, good. I'm glad
you're feeling confident.
I'll do all I can to protect you
to repay you for buying me this knife!
It's my job to protect you.
Monster: Patchwork Bear
There it is. It's a Patchwork Bear.
Its appearance is cute,
but its level, not so much.
It has an Attack of 22.
Even if you get hit somehow,
you'll survive.
You can't take a crit,
but I can shut it down by throwing it
off balance as it begins its attack.
How do you know all that?
Huh?
Do you like Patchwork Bears?
Not really.
I'll handle its attacks.
Ruche, attack from its
blind spots and take it down.
O-Okay.
Watch out for its claws and fangs.
Okay.
Shadow Stomp!
Shadow Stomp
I bought this skill using the skill points
I gained from fighting the Mad Headder.
Shadow Stomp
Step on a target's shadow to prevent
them from fleeing. The effect ends as
soon as your foot is no longer touching
the ground
I'll use this to help Ruche level up.
Shadows stretch farther
than you think. Be careful.
Got it.
Huh? You said to watch out
for its claws and fangs,
but it doesn't seem to have either.
What?!
I'm glad I have this shield.
Surviving attacks
without moving my feet is a pain.
Okay, Ruche. Keep hitting it.
R-Right!
It's not even cute anymore!
That took a lot of attacks.
But we managed to defeat it.
Ruche, how many levels did you gain?
What?!
No way!
Mr. Patchwork Bear, please drop something!
I'm going to be
kicked out of my party again!
Don't worry.
We just killed it for the EXP.
Huh?
I plan to kill a few more,
so something will drop eventually.
Speak of the devil.
Same plan. Let's go.
Got it!
There's another one!
Look, we got something!
They dropped items. Two in a row, too!
Bear Shield.
Bear Shield [Recommended Level: 10]
Defense: +12
Market Price: 200,000G
A cute round bear shield
Low recommended level for its stats
Defense +12.
Market price: 200,000 gold.
A cute round Bear Shield.
Aren't you glad you brought me?
You are, aren't you?
Are these useful, Mr. Elymas?
What? Oh, uh...
Well, we might as well take them.
Yes, good idea.
That's odd. These items don't
usually drop one after another.
Did I misremember
the drop rate? No, but...
Special Skill
Cat's Paw
Ruche's Cat's Paw is a special skill
that increases Luck by 500%.
Luck
If Ruche's starting Luck stat was high
to begin with, this isn't impossible.
I wasn't expecting
a Blood-Soaked Sword to drop.
It's because of my skills, you know.
I'm not sure that it really was
because of your skills.
Then why didn't Cline's party realize
how much she improved their drop rate?
You're so weak. Do you really think
you'll get a cut of the sale?
Oh, right. They just didn't realize her
value because they're a newbie party.
In this world, there isn't
a lot of information on monsters.
They must've gotten used to
high drop rates from the start.
Was I useful, Mr. Elymas?
Yeah. Ruche, thanks for
teaming up with me.
Did you want these
Bear Shields that badly?
Shall we collect ten of them today?
No, you've gained enough levels.
The real work starts now.
What?
Level 20 reached.
Wow, you're right. When did that happen?
Our new goal is hunting Golden Raana.
G-Golden Raana?!
Translator:
Sho Stifler
Timer:
Krzysztof Kunc
Editor:
Salem Alabanza
Quality Control:
Gabriella Alabanza
Final Quality Control:
Sriram Gurunathan
Ruche's power is even greater
than I expected.
No, this is still only
a fraction of her power.
No, I don't mean the Bear Shield.
I'm not equipping that.
In any case, now we can pursue our
actual goal for visiting the dungeon.
The real work starts now.
Next time, "Golden Raana Farming."
Every game needs a bonus character!